Contact

bernaldakfritton@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/bernaldafritton-msn-rn-cen-cmsrn-3aa865a3 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Clinical Research

BLS

ACLS

Certifications

Medical Surgical Nurse Certification Certified Emergency Nurse (CEN)

Bernalda Fritton MSN, RN, CEN, CMSRN

Certified Emergency Nurse (CEN) Certified Medical-Surgical Nurse (CMSRN)

Lincoln, Nebraska

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Health Insurance, Clinical Research, Patient Advocacy, Medical-Surgical, and Patient Education. Strong healthcare services professional with a Master's Degree focused in Nursing Administration from Loyola University New Orleans.

Experience

CHI St. Elizabeth

5 years

Emergency Room Nurse July 2015 - Present (5 years)

Lincoln, Nebraska Area

Registered Nurse

July 2015 - Present (5 years)

Emergency Department

Current supplemental staff in the Emergency Department.

JOHNSON COUNTY HOSPITAL

Registered Nurse

September 2016 - Present (3 years 10 months)

Tecumseh. NE

Current supplemental staff in a critical access hospital setting.

CMH Community Memorial Hospital Nurse Coordinator May 2017 - January 2019 (1 year 9 months) Syracuse, NE Huntington Hospital, Huntington, NY 11743 Registered Nurse July 2013 - July 2015 (2 years 1 month)

New York Institute of Technology Clinical Instructor September 2014 - December 2014 (4 months)

Lenox Hill Hospital Registered Nurse November 2011 - July 2013 (1 year 9 months) 4 Uris

Regional West Health Services
Registered Nurse
March 2011 - November 2011 (9 months)

Education

University of Nebraska Medical Center

Post Master's Certification , Family Nurse Pracitioner · (2019 - 2022)

City University of New York-John Jay College of Criminal Justice Bachelor's Degree, Criminology

Loyola University New Orleans

Master's Degree, Nursing Administration

Loyola University New Orleans Master's degree, Nursing's

Nassau Community College
Associate's Degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse